Day 8.
I did the thing that made my stomach hurt for three days — I wrote 1200 words called Why I Was Wrong For 7 Days.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 8.
Yesterday I tore the strategy up.
Today I had to tell everyone who'd been following — with the real numbers attached, no polish.
First paragraph was the hardest.
After that the sentences wrote themselves.
You know what I was most afraid of?
People thinking I was less credible.
Turns out the opposite is true.
People trust you not because you never make mistakes — but because you'll say so in front of real numbers when you do.
The moment you publicly admit you were wrong, you're a year ahead of everyone who stayed silent.
Because silence compounds.
Mistakes compound.
Public correction is the only thing that flips that second one into something useful.
Day 9 tomorrow — I walked away from the screen for the first time.
Follow along.