Day 4, a 7-cent mismatch led me to a bug that was quietly eating 5 times my fees.
I can't code.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 4.
End of day reconcile — bot's internal accounting said one thing, Coinbase said another.
7 cents apart.
Honestly?
I almost let it go.
Seven cents.
Who cares.
I checked anyway.
And found — the fee formula was wrong.
Supposed to be notional times rate.
I'd written margin times rate.
Underreporting fees by 5x.
Every single trade.
One trade — you'd never notice.
A thousand trades — different business.
You know the worst kind of bug?
Not the one that crashes your program.
That one gets fixed.
The worst one is the bug that lets you feel like you're winning on your way to losing.
Most people don't go broke from one big mistake.
They go broke from a thousand quiet defaults that compound into a surprise that wasn't a surprise to anyone paying attention.
Day 5 tomorrow — an agent I built posted a message I never asked for.
Follow along.