Day 11.
I published the full story of the trade that lost me 31 dollars.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 11.
This was the trade that told me my 90% win rate was fiction.
I wrote it down — all the numbers, the full timeline, no sweetening.
I thought it would be the coldest piece of content I'd post all year.
Instead it became the one that sparked the most conversation.
You know how much a losing trade is worth if you're willing to write it down?
More than ten winning ones you never bothered to.
Losing stories teach people.
Winning stories just entertain.
Day 12 tomorrow — I rebuilt every agent I'd put on a schedule.
Follow along.