Day 10.
I woke up and Twitter had taken my account.
No warning.
No reason given.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 10.
The moment it happened, I realized every thread I'd written, every follower, every receipt I'd posted — all of it, held by one platform that didn't call first.
Same day I did something that sounded unrelated — I launched bilingual mode on my own website.
At the time it felt small.
The week I had nowhere else to speak, it stopped feeling small.
There's a sentence I'd heard for years and always dismissed as cheesy — don't build your most valuable thing on top of ground you don't own.
That day, that sentence became an invoice.
From Day 10 on — my own site is home base.
Every other platform is just distribution.
The kind that can be turned off at any time.
Day 11 tomorrow — I wrote the full story of Trade number 267.
Follow along.