Day 9.
For the first time, I didn't watch the charts.
The bot made three trades.
I checked once.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 9.
That day I spent rewriting the website.
Reframed every line from trading product to social experiment.
Meanwhile, the bot made three trades on its own.
Net down about a dollar eighty.
I looked once.
Then closed the tab.
Not because I didn't care.
Because I'd finally built something I could stop policing.
The real test of any system you build is — can you stop watching it?
If you can't, you didn't build a system.
You built a second job.
Most people can't tell the difference.
That was the first day I rented my attention back from the bot.
It was cheaper than I expected.
Day 10 tomorrow — Twitter took my account without warning.
Follow along.