Day 14.
Fixed yesterday's 40 dollar bug with 3 lines of code.
Then added a second witness that never sleeps.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 14.
The fix was simple — replace my regular market sell with Coinbase's built-in close-position endpoint.
It auto-detects direction.
Physically cannot leave a residual.
Three lines.
For me, three words.
But the code fix alone wasn't the real answer.
The reason yesterday's bug could hide for 5.5 hours — my monitoring system and the bot's brain were the same brain.
So I built one more thing — a reconciler that runs every 15 minutes.
It doesn't listen to what the bot says.
It just compares two lists —
how many trades in the database?
How many fills on Coinbase?
If they don't match, it wakes me up.
Anything that matters — you need a second witness.
One that doesn't share your assumptions.
Day 15 tomorrow — first clean profit.
Follow along.