Day 1 ended.
Zero trades.
Zero profit.
And I learned more than 7 days of paper testing ever taught me.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
7 days ago I asked AI to build me a trading bot.
I put a thousand down for this experiment — if it works, any ordinary person can use it.
This is Day 1 of AI trading my thousand dollars.
Today it trades with my real money for the first time.
One word in the config — paper to live — real money starts.
I changed it, and stared at the Enter key for 20 minutes.
Then this thought hits me — if this loses everything tonight, how do I tell anyone?
That thought, in paper mode, never once crossed my mind.
Not once.
I pressed.
Nothing happened.
One hour, no trade.
Two hours, still nothing.
It was waiting for a signal.
I was waiting for it.
By hour three my eyes hurt.
So I washed dishes.
Halfway through the sink, I realized I'd relaxed.
Something had shifted.
I couldn't have told you what.
Day 1.
Zero trades.
But most of what I learned all week came from those three hours.
Day 2 tomorrow — it actually traded.
Follow if you want to see what happened next.