Day 2 earned me 3 cents.
But the real cost was the three things I found.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
I gave AI a thousand dollars to trade for me.
Day 2.
Around noon it placed its first real trade — bought one SOL contract at eighty-two seventy-six, sold it minutes later.
Balance went from one thousand to nine ninety-nine oh three.
Fees took 97 cents.
Sounds like nothing, right?
But in those two minutes of watching, I noticed three things I'd been pretending not to see.
One — the grid module.
Supposed to be live.
Still simulating orders.
I'd thought about whether this might break when I wrote the spec.
I decided probably not.
Two — seven of my backend servers bound to zero-zero-zero-zero.
Open to the entire internet.
For a week.
Nothing bad had happened.
But nothing bad yet isn't the same as nothing bad ever.
Three — a source file I'd pushed to public GitHub.
My phone number, hardcoded.
A three-cent profit exposed three pieces of work I'd been avoiding.
In paper mode you never see these.
Real skin on the line is the only thing that shows them to you.
Day 3 tomorrow — I decided to give everything away for free.
Follow along.