Day 7.
I deleted a week's worth of code.
Why?
Because it had been right for the wrong reason.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 7.
After yesterday's 90 percent win rate illusion collapsed, I made the most against-my-own-instincts decision I could — delete.
Not bugs.
The things I'd been right about.
A week of work.
I hardcoded the grid feature off inside the system config.
No future version of the code can turn it back on without me physically editing the system file.
Ulysses pact with my future self.
Then I wrote a new house rule — every strategy change requires a 90-day backtest before it touches a dollar.
No exceptions.
Performers protect their past rightness.
Learners replace it.
The ability to burn something you were right about — that's the thing that separates real learning from performance.
Day 8 tomorrow — I told everyone I was wrong.
Follow along.