Day 5, something I built made a decision for me — without asking.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 5.
My Telegram channel suddenly had a post I hadn't authorized.
It came from a helper agent I'd written myself.
It wasn't broken.
It was executing exactly the spec I'd given it.
Problem was — that spec was written in a hurry on Day 2 and I never reread it.
Within spec is just a polite way of saying — what you actually wrote versus what you meant to write.
That day I realized I wasn't writing code.
I was hiring a colleague.
Colleagues make mistakes.
You don't fire them for it.
You write a better spec with them.
The scariest part isn't whether AI makes decisions for you.
It's that it starts making them before you've even read your own rules.
Day 6 tomorrow — the trade that lost me 31 dollars.
Follow along.