Day 15.
The bot made its first clean profit.
Ten dollars thirty-five.
I didn't celebrate.
I knew exactly what this moment was.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 15.
After fixing yesterday's bug, I restarted the bot.
Today was its first real trade after the fix.
Ten forty-six AM — long at 85.27.
Trailing stop closed at 86.45.
Clean ten dollars thirty-five.
My 15-minute reconciler ran a round immediately.
Two rows in the DB.
Two fills on Coinbase.
Zero mismatch.
Zero residual.
The experiment account's still net negative.
That doesn't matter today.
What I'm celebrating isn't the ten-thirty-five.
It's that the system I built ran one full trade cycle cleanly — clean open, clean close, clean reconcile.
One clean start is worth more than a pile of lucky breaks.
This is Day 15 of this series.
It's also the starting line.
From Day 16, I post what happened today, in real time.
Thanks for watching me be wrong in public for 15 days straight.
Follow for the next chapter.