Day 13.
I lost 40 dollars to a position that didn't exist.
My own bot had lied to me for five and a half hours.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 13.
The bot hit a stop loss.
Fired a market sell to close the long.
From its point of view — closed.
Problem was — the order it sent to Coinbase had no close flag.
The exchange treated it as a brand new short.
Result?
Long got netted.
Short got opened.
Five and a half hours later I opened the app manually and found it.
What scared me wasn't the 40 dollars.
It was — every monitor I had said everything was fine.
The bot's logs said okay.
Risk said okay.
You could only see the ghost from outside the system.
The most dangerous kind of failure is the one that doesn't announce itself.
It doesn't crash, doesn't error, doesn't warn.
It just quietly makes your numbers slightly wrong.
Day 14 tomorrow — I fixed it with 3 lines of code.
Follow along.