Day 12.
I noticed something — my automated agents were still telling last week's story.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 12.
I looked at the four agents running in the background — the tweet-writer, the long-form poster, the interview bot, the comment collector.
All of them were speaking in the voice I'd written a week ago.
That voice was built on top of the strategy I'd already killed.
Meaning — my mouth had changed.
My stand-ins were still reading from the old script.
When the story changes direction, every automation still speaking the old direction has to change with it.
Including the automated versions of yourself.
Otherwise you'll contradict yourself in your sleep.
That day I wiped all four agents and rewrote them from scratch.
Every new prompt starts from one phrase: if I can, you can.
Day 13 tomorrow — the bot lied about closing my position.
Follow along.