Day 16.
I found a number in my account.
Fifty-seven dollars.
It was already gone.
I hadn't lost a single trade yet.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 16.
For 15 days I'd been watching win rate and outcomes.
62 trades, 48 percent — within what I thought was fixable.
Then that afternoon I added another column — fees 30.
Funding 27.
Combined, 57 dollars.
My real trading losses were only 14.
Which means: even if I made zero mistakes, the account would still be bleeding — because holding a position costs rent.
I'd stared at that 14 dollars for 15 days.
The 57 that actually put me in the red was the column I hadn't looked at.
If you optimize the wrong column, more effort makes it worse.
Day 17 tomorrow — I shipped a rule I don't trust myself.
Follow along.