Day 3 I made a decision most people told me was dumb — I gave everything away for free.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI's trading my thousand dollars.
Day 3.
I had a choice that day — turn this into a paid product, or make it a public experiment.
I picked the expensive one.
13 lessons, free.
Live balance, free.
Every trade, every win rate, every drawdown — free.
The only thing behind the paywall — the specific parameters that would let a copycat clone the strategy.
A friend asked me — you're burning your own bridge, you know that, right?
I told him no.
This is the only honest promise I can make.
Because if I'm wrong, I want everyone to watch me be wrong in real time.
And if I'm right, same thing.
Want people to trust what you're building?
Let them watch it work for free, first.
Day 4 tomorrow — the bug I almost didn't check.
Follow along.