Day 6.
I lost 31 dollars.
Then I found something worse — the 90 percent win rate I'd been citing in public all week was basically fiction.
I can't code.
9 years in crypto.
AI trades my thousand.
Day 6.
The bot hit a stop loss.
Single trade loss of 31 dollars.
First real loss of the experiment.
I sat down to review.
On a whim I stretched the backtest window from 5 days to 13 months.
Same strategy — 13 months.
Minus 46 percent return.
Minus 56 percent max drawdown.
Translation — the 90 percent win rate I'd been proud of for a week was a number hiding in the narrowest possible window.
Not dishonest.
Just incomplete.
And incomplete when money's involved means — wrong.
You know what your proudest number usually looks like?
It's usually hiding in the corner you don't want to stretch.
Stretching the window is the scariest thing you can do to yourself.
Your number might survive.
It might not.
You don't know till you look.
I looked.
It didn't survive.
Day 7 tomorrow — I decided to tear the whole thing apart.
Follow along.